export const data = {
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How would you describe your sleep patterns?",
      "options": [
        "Consistently restful+0",
        "Occasionally disrupted+1",
        "Frequently disrupted+2",
        "Persistent insomnia+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Consistently restful"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long does it typically take you to fall asleep after getting into bed?",
      "options": [
        "Falls asleep quickly+0",
        "Within 15-30 minutes+1",
        "Within 30-60 minutes+2",
        "More than an hour+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Falls asleep quickly"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often do you wake up during the night and have difficulty going back to sleep?",
      "options": [
        "Rarely or never+0",
        "Occasionally+1",
        "Frequently+2",
        "Almost every night+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Rarely or never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you wake up early in the morning and find it hard to go back to sleep?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with insomnia or sleep-related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Yes+3",
        "Considering it+2",
        "No, not yet+1",
        "No, and I don't plan to+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Considering it"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do sleep issues impact your daily life and activities?",
      "options": [
        "Low impact+0",
        "Moderate impact+1",
        "High impact+2",
        "Very high impact+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Low impact"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you often feel fatigued or have difficulty concentrating during the day due to lack of sleep?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Have others expressed concern about your sleep patterns or insomnia-related issues?",
      "options": [
        "Never+0",
        "Rarely+1",
        "Sometimes+2",
        "Frequently+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Never"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing insomnia is important for overall well-being?",
      "options": [
        "Strongly agree+3",
        "Agree+2",
        "Neutral+1",
        "Disagree+0"
      ],
      "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
    },
    {
      "question": "How long have you been experiencing sleep-related difficulties?",
      "options": [
        "A short period+0",
        "Several months+1",
        "Years+2",
        "I haven't experienced sleep-related difficulties+3"
      ],
      "correctOption": "I haven't experienced sleep-related difficulties"
    }
  ]
}
